[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Did you find out who the person helping us is?
What does he want in return?
He can do that? And why does he want Chiara in return?
What he wants
is to overthrow the President of the Philippines.
I just thought it would be better if I took the initiative
and found out who this agency's enemies are.
Tell me right away.
Because I want to know what you're doing.
He's not just some ordinary guy, sweetheart.
Almost like the way Donatello and I used to move.
I'm worried there might be another threat coming.
Sweetheart. La Morte Bianca is gone.
So just relax, okay?
Nothing will get in our way anymore.
He's not just planning to take down the Moravianos,
he's slowly building Sinigang Cartel 2.0.
So it's not just the senator we're watching.
We're also watching a new syndicate being born.
I thought you'd forgotten about me.
You really know how to drop a punchline.
I think you're spending too much time with that senator.
So why did you call?
And I hope you'll be honest this time.
Will my family be left alone?
Did you know more people get into accidents
than get killed by syndicates?
Norberto, don't give me that crap.
Of all people, you should know
that once you've stepped into a syndicate,
you always have to watch your back.
That's not true.
Look at me.
I got out of that messed-up life.
Is that what you tell yourself every day?
You did escape your messed-up life back then.
But you know, it will catch up with you.
So look at me.
I chose to stay in the service.
I chose to fight.
I can't run from the wrongs I've done in my life.
So here I am,
facing my own ghosts from the past.
Mario.
No matter what happened between us,
I still consider you a friend.
Not just as a friend, but as a father.
As soon as I get any information
that says there's a threat or danger to Mikoy and Chiara's lives,
you'll be the very first to know.
Thank you, my friend.
I look forward to it.
Rahmboy!
-Brothers. -Whoa!
You're getting good at chopping!
The axe doesn't even get stuck in the wood anymore.
Mario taught me, Mikoy.
He said you can't just keep chopping away.
You've got to position yourself right and know where to put your force.
And there's also a timing to splitting the wood.
It's like dancing, right, guys?
-You need the right rhythm. -What a punchline.
You know, it's kind of like life.
Right? Sometimes,
life is just life.
-That was lame! -That was lame!
-Come on. -What was that?
That made no sense. I thought it was going somewhere.
Hey, wait. Why'd you stop?
No, bro. I was just happy for you guys.
You guys just seem so happy, like you don't have a care in the world.
No, that's just how we are.
-Yes. -That's how we were raised.
Not just by our parents,
but by our neighbors, our friends,
even the people we know.
And it's not that hard to be happy even in the middle of problems.
As long as I don't have toxic people around me.
That's the best part.
You guys are so fun.
I hope I get to experience that too.
He's getting all emotional!
So sentimental!
What, are you gonna open up now?
What, are we having an open forum now?
-Yes. -Go ahead.
-It's just us anyway. We're all guys here. -Exactly.
No, I just miss my mom.
Where is your mother, Rahmboy?
She's an OFW, in Hong Kong.
Hong Kong, huh?
Chiara and I just got back from there.
We might've even seen your mother there.
That was five years ago, bro.
-Is that so? -Oh, five years ago.
So where is she now?
My mom.
Hello, Mom. We miss you!
Mom, I'm a size 10!
-Ma, I'm a size 7! -What size 7?
You guys, seriously. Here, take this.
These guys might ask her to send them money next.
Thank you, bro.
Ma, sorry it's so noisy.
I'm fine. I'm with them.
-Oh, no! -Why?
My fiancée left her water bottle behind again.
I need to deliver it to her.
-What, is there no water there? -Exactly.
You guys don't get it.
Her water bottle has lemon, chia seeds, psyllium husk,
collagen, electrolytes, ginkgo biloba, and Shirota strain.
If she doesn't drink that,
I'm sure we're all screwed again.
-We're screwed? -We're screwed?
Of course, you're coming down with me!
Where's her water bottle with all that stuff you mentioned?
There it is.
Let's find it.
Let's go!
Goodness!
Agent Alex, I'm so excited to see Chiara wearing her wedding gown.
So this is what it feels like when someone in the family is getting married.
You know, Agent,
I feel like I'm the one getting married.
Is that normal?
Of course, Miss Tess.
You've grown attached to Chiara too.
And you've come to think of her as your daughter too.
Exactly.
So in a sense, it's like your daughter who's getting married too.
Mom!
Mikoy, what are you doing here?
-Are you the one fitting the gown? -No, Mom.
Chiara texted me.
She left her water bottle behind.
You know how it is.
That bottle is basically her emotional support bottle.
She might transform if she doesn't get to do her little water regimen, right?
Oh, right.
Miss Tess, Chiara's calling you.
My other daughter is calling me. I'll leave you two for now.
Hey.
Thanks, okay?
For what now?
Lately, you keep thanking me.
For everything.
For being here.
For things like this.
Because Chiara doesn't always have to hear
my opinion, right?
It's important that she can talk to people outside our relationship.
People who aren't my relatives.
Like you. Right?
So she can let out all the stress she's dealing with in life.
Even if it's about me.
You know?
In short, so she's free to bash you.
Pretty much.
But I'm not perfect, you know?
Of course I'm in love with Chiara, but I'm not perfect.
Of course, there are things I might do that she won't like.
I don't want her to keep all of that to herself.
You two really are perfect for each other.
Thank you, Alex.
Guys, Chiara's ready!
Mikoy, why are you still here?
You can't see Chiara wearing her wedding gown.
It's bad luck.
Your mom's right. Come on, Mikoy, go for now.
-Okay, just give this to Chiara. -Sure.
Go on.
-Leonela, come on. Come with me. -Go ahead, Miss Tess.
Oh, no, Mikoy! You're not allowed to look!
It's bad luck!
Did I come to the right building?
The place is right, and so is the schedule.
But why does something feel wrong?
Did I miss an announcement?
You got that right.
You missed the announcement that there's no meeting today.
I knew it.
So you knew there was no meeting?
I knew it. I'm the newest one to get kicked out of the group chat,
then they made a new group chat and didn't invite me.
It's so annoying. It pisses me off.
I've got your back.
I'll get updates from your classmates,
then I'll DM you if there are any special announcements like this.
And you know what?
Sometimes it's better to have fewer group chats.
Because think about it, all you'll see
is nonstop noise, gossip, and spam messages anyway.
It's better this way.
Thank you, Laurence, for offering to help, but you know,
I can handle this.
I know who's behind all this.
It's that girl.
Why should I adjust when I'm the one being bullied?
And why should I be scared?
Just because I got kicked out of the group chat?
Luisa Mae.
-So, did it arrive? -It did.
Oh, sweetheart, you look absolutely beautiful!
Your wedding gown looks perfect on you.
One step closer to becoming Mrs. Pinagpala.
And one step closer to the life you've always dreamed of.
A life that used to be just a dream.
You prayed for it, and look at you now.
There you are, already wearing your wedding gown.
It's just sad that you're not here, Ma, Pa.
I know this was a dream for you too, but…
it's okay even if you're not here.
I can still feel how much you love me.
Darling, I still need to make some adjustments to your wedding gown.
I'm not satisfied yet, and I'm still not happy with it.
Oh, sweetheart, your seamstress seems like a perfectionist.
That's a good thing because if it were me,
I'd want every adjustment to be perfect too.
So have her fix it until your wedding gown is perfect, okay?
Yes, your mama is right, sweetheart.
-I love you, sweetheart! -I love you, sweetheart!
I'll give this to Mommy Tess.
‎And a little bit longer.
Chiara, Chiara, come here for a moment.
It looks like someone wants to have a few things changed,
some things added or altered. Alex has a few suggestions.
It's up to you if you want to, but I was thinking it might look better if…
Where's Viktor? He has a delivery from the senator.
Huh?!
Are you looking for Sir Viktor?
Why are you shouting? I'm right in front of you.
When I was taking a shower earlier,
I think water got into my ear.
So I'm not sure if I'm speaking too softly
or too loudly.
Are you looking for Sir Viktor?
Yes.
Sir Viktor!
What is it?
Here it is, right?
We're almost there.
We'll officially be in-laws soon.
After everything we've been through,
our families really are getting a happy ending.
Thank you, in-law.
For being there for Chiara,
while we're here, and I'm here,
paying for the sins of a married couple.
Thank you for taking care of her,
for listening to her.
For being there when it should've been me, because I'm her mother.
Oh, in-law.
Chiara is like a daughter to me now.
You know, she's not hard to love.
She's not hard to take care of either.
Didn't I tell you? We'll make it to our happy ending.
And besides, hello?
Don't worry, I am so sure
you'll see each other and be together again.
Our families are getting a happy ending,
and you're going to have a happy ending where you're crying and feeling sad?
Hey, Luisa Mae.
Enough with pretending to be the sweet girl, nice girl,
and good girl.
And you actually brought a sidekick.
Seriously?
Don't you have any originality?
So you might as well know your place.
I'll know my place, all right.
And, you know, I'm protecting myself too,
and that's called self-defense.
And what you did by kicking me out of the group chat,
that's bullying.
And I won't let you just do whatever you want to me,
especially when it's wrong.
So, can you?
Enough.
Well, you don't get to tell me when to stop
because I'm just getting started, Sofie.
Because starting today,
you, Sofia Anikka Ruiz,
are considered a persona non grata.
What the hell is a persona non grata?
Are you the city or something and you have executive power?
Wow, that's a lot!
If you don't like the term "persona non grata",
fine, let's make it simple.
You know, you really have no originality.
That's from F4.
You know what? That's enough.
You know, that's the price you pay for messing with the queen bee.
And you know what? You're right.
Okay, what's the plan?
Why do we have to be in formation?
-Nothing. Discreet matters. -Okay.
Discreet? Why does it have to be discreet?
Because we're planning your stag party, bro.
Right?
Wait, are you guys serious?
No, I don't want that.
Why?
Wait, wait.
Then why is he still here?
-Exactly. -This is a surprise.
-This is a surprise. You're not invited. -Go inside, go inside.
Bro, wait. Go inside. We'll call you later. Just wait.
Okay, here. Here's our plan.
Just keep in mind our budget, 1,500 only, so we can have more.
Yes.
-Is that possible? -That's enough money.
Don't cry, my love.
Everything will be all right.
We'll get out of here eventually.
I know.
I just can't accept that as her mother,
I'm not by my daughter's side
for the most important event of her life.
We won't even be able to attend her wedding.
But we have to be happy for her.
So that she won't be sad either.
I know that.
There's nothing we can do
but be happy for her.
You need to come with us, Viktor Valtrovi.
-Take him. -What? Why?
-What's going on? -Where are you taking him?
-Where are you taking my husband? -Where are you taking me?
Hey, wait! Explain yourselves.
Come with us.
Where are you taking him?
What, aren't you going to answer?
-Where are you taking my husband? -Hey! What's going on?
-Don't worry. -What is it this time?
-Viktor! Where are you taking my husband? -Where are you taking Sir Viktor?
-Hang on! -Viktor!
Don't worry, ma'am. I'll take care of Sir Viktor.
Sir Viktor!
-Viktor! -Hey!
Wait!
I'm Sir Viktor's plus-one.
We're like B1 and B2!
We're always together.
Wherever he is, I'm there!
Remember that!
Suit yourself!
Then you two can suffer together with no relief in sight. Get in!
-Okay, okay. Easy. -Go!
Come on.
So there we go. We're all set, okay?
Thank you!
So, Chiara, are you okay with the changes we added?
Of course. Actually, I'm so thankful to you.
My fairy maid of honor.
Because I've really been nervous about my wedding,
but because all of you are here for me,
I'm excited now.
I'm sure you'll be the most beautiful woman on that day.
Leonela, come on. Come with us.
Oh, no. You guys go ahead. Go ahead.
I still have somewhere to go.
I have something to take care of with the catering.
Thank you so much.
-Thank you, thank you, everyone. -Thank you. We'll go ahead.
Take care.
You're here?
Do you need me to pick you up?
How about this? Let's not see each other yet, okay?
Hey, Carlota.
What are you doing here?
Waiting for you.
Didn't I tell you to meet me here?
So we could go in together.
Okay, sure. Shall we?
Shall we?
GLOBAL AGENCY FOR GOVERNMENT OPERATIONS
Did you know it's been a while since I last had a foot spa?
But believe me, this call is an urgent matter.
I have an update about that video and that mysterious vigilante.
-Mario, Captain is looking for you. -Why? Did something happen?
It's about the Manananggal?
I'll just change my clothes.
-And I'll follow you to barangay hall. -All right.
-About that again. -And why the rush?
Who were you talking to earlier?
What are you hiding, Sianong?
Why do I only see your red flags now?
Mom?
Mama Yaya?